aceproject.com 2010-02-11

# Privacy Policy Statement

|   
---  
| 

Privacy Policy Statement

This privacy statement covers the site [www.aceproject.com]. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to its users' privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices. 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact Daniel Raymond by email at [support@aceproject.com](mailto:support@aceproject.com). 

|   
|  |  |   | 

**Information Collection and Use**  
  
---|---  
|   | 

**Information Collection**  
[[Websystems Inc.](http://www.websystems-inc.com/)] is the sole owner of the information collected on [www.aceproject.com]. [[Websystems Inc.](http://www.websystems-inc.com/)] collects information from its users at several different points on our Web site.

**Registration**  
In order to use this Web site, a user must first create a free account. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to send requested email notifications, to contact our customers for major announcements or to fix account-related issues, such as payment issues.

**Order**  
Our partner, [Internet Secure](http://www.internetsecure.com/), requests information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If [Internet Secure](http://www.internetsecure.com/) has trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

|    
---|---|---  
   
  | 

**Profile**  
We store information that we collect through cookies and dynamic asp pages to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that detail their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users' personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site. We do not share users profiles with other third parties.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use cookies to remember your Account ID, username and password. We do not share your cookie with other third parties.

**Dynamic ASP Pages**  
We use dynamic ASP forms to collect information like company information, projects, timesheets, users, tasks, files attachments, notes, and preferences. We do not share your information with other third parties.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movements in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our Web-based service. We use a tracking utility called [Google Analytics ](http://www.google.com/analytics/) that uses log files to analyze user movement. 

**Password Encryption**  
Passwords are encrypted with the "md5" crytographic algorhitm. Thus, passwords are case sensitive and are visible neither by us nor by your account's administrators. This puts the level of security of your data at a very high level. If your forgot your password, you will have to use the "Forgot Password?" link to enter a new one, since it cannot be retreived.

|    
   
|   | 

**Communication from the Site**  
  
---|---  
  | 

We do not share users' emails with other third parties, we do not spam, and we do not offer an ad-supported software as a service.

**Special Offers and Updates**  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify email, username, and password. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.

**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send users an email or put an alert on the login page. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

**Customer Service**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

**Email Notification**  
Each user may decide to receive an email when he or she is assigned to a new task, or when one of his or her tasks is modified. This frees the project manager's time for more important tasks - email notification is automatic.

|    
   
  | 

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

These are the instances in which we will share users' personal information:

**Business Transitions**  
In the event that [[Websystems Inc.](http://www.websystems-inc.com/)] goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email, a prominent notice would be placed on our Web site for 30 days, prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If, as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying with "unsubscribe" in the subject line in the email or email us at [support@aceproject.com](mailto:support@aceproject.com).

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, [[Websystems Inc.](http://www.websystems-inc.com/)], are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Security**  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When [Internet Secure](http://www.internetsecure.com/) registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption technology in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as the [Internet Secure](http://www.internetsecure.com/) order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox, becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done from the "Account information page" or by emailing our Customer Service at [support@aceproject.com](mailto:support@aceproject.com).

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we can use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

|    
   
|  | 

**Contact Information**  
  
---|---  
|   | 

**Customer Service** \- For general inquiries about your account, our packages or about the software navigation.

|    
---|---|---  

Email: [ support@aceproject.com](mailto:support@aceproject.com)  
**Phone (Toll free for US and Canada):**   
866.259.2454 / +1.418.907.5184 (International) Fax: +1.418.907.8089  
We are available between 9 A.M. and 5 P.M. [GMT -5 Eastern Standard Time], Monday to Friday.  

|  |  | 

**Mailing Address**  
  
---|---  
|   | 

Websystems Inc.  
6655, Pierre-Bertrand Blvd.  
Door #4, Office #240  
Quebec, QC  
Canada G2K 1M1

|    
---|---|---  
   
  |    
  |   |    
|  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |
